once we have the tools for massive
collaboration we've unleashed humanity
as individuals on our collective
problems which means as individuals you
get to choose where you want your time
and energy to be spent what calls to you
and find groups of people to work on it
with which means individuals get a geek
out in the area of their choosing we get
to have historians working on ways to
make history exciting and fun and
available to us and in same with
politics and economics and science and
current events when a current event
happens you can find a group of people
to have an actual real real world impact
to help recreate a society that's been
that's been devastated by a natural
disaster empowering them with the tools
to recreate their society we can like
the sky is the limit for what we can
create together because there's no
amount there's no limit to our human
ingenuity there's no limit to what we
are capable of we're just not organized
yet we just don't have the ability to
find the place that we fit the best it's
all left up to chance and competition
instead of organized cooperation we have
the tools for organized cooperation we
can create it all so fast when every new
person who has an idea it doesn't have
to take the risk that they're not going
to have the right marketing or find the
right funding and keep it going
when we solve marketing and funding for
together tech we've solved it for all of
our individual problems and we're not
overspending and over extending our
human capacity before we're capable if
we don't have enough people and money to
work on all the projects which you
probably won't in the beginning even
after we've had the massive
collaboration tool we pick one project
we work on it well still allowing the
individuals to have conversations and
start problem-solving on the on the
niche area that they want to even if
it's not the one that's currently being
funded they can still start having a
conversation for free still work on
project management possibly do their own
crowdfunding if they really want it off
the off the ground right away
we can have tools to compare what
already exists in every sector what's
the best source of energy if you're
creating your own your own community so
you're not using the energy off the grid
what's the best source of water
filtration of plumbing then looking at
well how what is the maintenance on that
like we can compare what already exists
create space create what doesn't already
exist taking the good out of all of it
and minimizing the bad making sure that
the parts are available to constantly be
doing the improvement for a lifetime if
we've created it together we can make
sure those things are available we can
make the Lego bricks of life that are
yes like a bricks of life that you know
that these components are available and
you can make anything out of these
components we can create a world that
actually works for everyone when we give
people the ability to come somewhere and
say what's not working for them and be
empowered with the tools to find the
people that's also not working for and
have a direct impact and problem solving
it without taking on massive risk of not
getting the funding of not staying in
business long enough and eroding the
trust for future projects this is why a
technology company that we all own
together and run together gives humanity
more power than we have ever had before
empowerment in your own life in your own
unique way because you get to say what
you want to keep powered on if you're
not feeling empowered why and how can we
help create the tools so you can so you
can understand the information if you're
not understanding it you'll find the
people if you can't find them by
yourself the sky's the limit to the
technology we can create together and
the more people come on board the more
people that there are to to bring money
to bring passion to bring their their
talents the faster it all happens but we
do it efficiently we do it in a way that
is organized cooperation instead of
chaotic competition and risky
competition a better world is on its way
and everybody who wants to gets to
participate in creating it